Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Netflix and chilled. Let me show
you how to make it.
>> Sweet, salty, chewy, crunchy.
Awesome.
>> So, we're doing a peanut butter base.
One of my favorite bases I've ever made.
It uses PB Fit, which is peanut butter
powder and [music] real peanut butter to
make it extra creamy. The full
ingredients will be down in the
description below. You're just going to
blend all of them up with an immersion
blender. Throw it in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Take it out, run out of
hot water for about a minute, and then
throw it in your creamy on the ice cream
set. And while we wait for that to spin,
let me just tell you, out of the 50 plus
Ben & Jerry's flavors I've recreated in
the Ninja Creamy, I think this is my
favorite. It's truly the epitome of
sweet and salty in an ice cream flavor.
And if you like peanut butter, you're
going to love this flavor. Now, let's
quickly talk about the toppings. I used
half of a Prime Bites protein brownie to
add a little bit of protein. These are a
great addition to any ice cream flavor.
And then about 10 grams of crushed
pretzels [music] to add some crunch and
a ton of saltiness.